Guide to the Farnam Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- HENRY FARNAM (1803-1883), 1721-1898; Series I; 37 linear feet (88 boxes)
  - Financial papers
    - Hillhouse Avenue home
      - Deed, 1872 (Box 87, Folder 923)
    - Sheffield Farm, 1853-1861 (Box 88, Folder 924-930)
    - Miscellanea, 1805-1811, undated (Box 88, Folder 931)
- HENRY W. FARNAM (1853-1933), 1841-1941; Series II; 112 linear feet (222 boxes)
  This series is arranged in eight sections: General correspondence, Select correspondence, Letterbooks, Financial papers, Financial circulars, Writings, Subject files, and Scrapbooks.
  General correspondence, Letterbooks, and Financial circulars are arranged in chronological order.
  Select correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the particular letter(s) of the alphabet, and chronologically for each such letter.
  Financial papers, Subject files, and Scrapbooks are arranged alphabetically by topic, while Writings is arranged by type.
  - General correspondence
    - 1884-1885 (Box 89, Folder 932-938)
    - 1885-1887 (Box 90, Folder 939-946)
    - 1887-1889 (Box 91, Folder 947-954)
    - 1889-1893 (Box 92, Folder 955-963)
    - 1893-1895 (Box 93, Folder 964-971)
    - 1895-1897 (Box 94, Folder 972-979)
    - 1897-1901 (Box 95, Folder 980-987)
    - 1902-1904 (Box 96, Folder 988-994)
    - 1904-1906 (Box 97, Folder 995-1002)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 98, Folder 1003-1009)
    - 1907-1908 (Box 99, Folder 1010-1016)
    - 1909 (Box 100, Folder 1017-1023)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 101, Folder 1024-1030)
    - 1910-1911 (Box 102, Folder 1031-1037)
    - 1911-1912 (Box 103, Folder 1032-1039)
    - 1912-1913 (Box 104, Folder 1040-1047)
    - 1913 (Box 105, Folder 1048-1054)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 106, Folder 1055-1061)
    - 1914-1915 (Box 107, Folder 1062-1068)
    - 1915 (Box 108, Folder 1069-1075)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 109, Folder 1076-1082)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 110, Folder 1083-1089)
    - 1917 (Box 111, Folder 1090-1096)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 112, Folder 1097-1103)
    - 1918 (Box 113, Folder 1104-1110)
    - 1918 (Box 114, Folder 1111-1117)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 115, Folder 1118-1124)
    - 1919 (Box 116, Folder 1125-1131)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 117, Folder 1132-1139)
    - 1920 (Box 118, Folder 1140-1146)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 119, Folder 1147-1153)
    - 1921 (Box 120, Folder 1154-1161)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 121, Folder 1162-1169)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 122, Folder 1170-1176)
    - 1923 (Box 123, Folder 1177-1183)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 124, Folder 1184-1190)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 125, Folder 1191-1197)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 126, Folder 1198-1204)
    - 1926 (Box 127, Folder 1205-1211)
    - 1927 (Box 128, Folder 1212-1218)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 129, Folder 1219-1225)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 130, Folder 1226-1232)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 131, Folder 1233-1239)
    - 1932-1941 (Box 132, Folder 1240-1246)
  - Select correspondence
    - A, 1884-1911 (Box 133, Folder 1247-1265)
    - A, 1912-1924 February (Box 134, Folder 1266-1276)
    - A, 1924 February-1939 (Box 135, Folder 1277-1283)
    - B, 1884-1896 June (Box 136, Folder 1284-1295)
    - B, 1896 July-1908 (Box 137, Folder 1296-1302)
    - B, 1909-1914 (Box 138, Folder 1303-1211)
    - B, 1915-1919 (Box 139, Folder 1312-1320)
    - B, 1920-1928 June (Box 140, Folder 1321-1331)
    - B, 1928 July-1939 (Box 141, Folder 1332-1336)
    - C, 1884-1897 June (Box 142, Folder 1337-1348)
    - C, 1897 July-1908 December (Box 143, Folder 1349-1354)
    - C, 1909-1915 (Box 144, Folder 1355-1363)
    - C, 1916-1922 October (Box 145, Folder 1364-1373)
    - C, 1922 November-1939 (Box 146, Folder 1374-1385)
    - D, 1884-1906 October (Box 147, Folder 1386-1402)
    - D, 1907 March-1918 (Box 148, Folder 1403-1412)
    - D, 1919-1939 (Box 149, Folder 1413-1423)
    - E, 1884-1932 (Box 150, Folder 1424-1449)
    - F, 1884-1900 (Box 151, Folder 1450-1463)
    - F, 1901-1910 February (Box 152, Folder 1464-1469)
    - F, 1910 March-1915 (Box 153, Folder 1470-1476)
    - F, 1916-1919 (Box 154, Folder 1477-1484)
    - F, 1920-1926 (Box 155, Folder 1485-1492)
    - F, 1927-1939 (Box 156, Folder 1493-1497)
    - G, 1884-1911 (Box 157, Folder 1498-1516)
    - G, 1912-1919 (Box 158, Folder 1517-1534)
    - H, 1884-1902 (Box 159, Folder 1535-1449)
    - H, 1903-1913 (Box 160, Folder 1550-1558)
    - H, 1914-1918 (Box 161, Folder 1559-1568)
    - H, 1919-1924 February (Box 162, Folder 1569-1576)
    - H, 1924 February-1932 (Box 163, Folder 1577-1589)
    - I-J, 1884-1911 March (Box 164, Folder 1590-1608)
    - I-J, 1911 March-1932 (Box 165, Folder 1609-1626)
    - K, 1884-1914 (Box 166, Folder 1627-1643)
    - K, 1915-1932 (Box 167, Folder 1644-1658)
    - L, 1884-1911 (Box 168, Folder 1659-1675)
    - L, 1912-1932 (Box 169, Folder 1676-1693)
    - M, 1884-1900 (Box 170, Folder 1694-1708)
    - M, 1901-1911 (Box 171, Folder 1709-1717)
    - M, 1912-1919 (Box 172, Folder 1718-1778)
    - M, 1920-1935 (Box 173, Folder 1729-1740)
    - N-O, 1884-1911 (Box 174, Folder 1741-1759)
    - N-O, 1912-1924 February (Box 175, Folder 1760-1770)
    - N-O, 1924 February-1935 (Box 176, Folder 1771-1777)
    - P-Q, 1884-1890 July (Box 177, Folder 1778-1783)
    - P-Q, 1890-July-1906 October (Box 178, Folder 1784-1794)
    - P-Q, 1907 March-1924 February (Box 179, Folder 1795-1808)
    - P-Q, 1924 February-1939 (Box 180, Folder 1809-1815)
    - R, 1884-1904 (Box 181, Folder 1816-1830)
    - R, 1905-1919 (Box 182, Folder 1831-1842)
    - R, 1920-1939 (Box 183, Folder 1843-1852)
    - S, 1884-1897 June (Box 184, Folder 1853-1864)
    - S, 1897 July-1908 (Box 185, Folder 1865-1871)
    - S, 1909-1914 (Box 186, Folder 1872-1880)
    - S, 1915-1922 October (Box 187, Folder 1881-1892)
    - S, 1922 November-1939 (Box 188, Folder 1893-1906)
    - T, 1884-1905 (Box 189, Folder 1907-1923)
    - T, 1906-1915 (Box 190, Folder 1924-1932)
    - T, 1916-1925 May (Box 191, Folder 1933-1941)
    - T, 1925 June-1942 (Box 192, Folder 1942-1947)
    - U-V, 1884-1924 February (Box 193, Folder 1948-1972)
    - U-V, 1924 February-1932 (Box 194, Folder 1973-1978)
    - W, 1884-1896 June (Box 195, Folder 1979-1990)
    - W, 1896 July-1908 (Box 196, Folder 1991-1998)
    - W, 1909-1915 (Box 197, Folder 1999-2008)
    - W, 1916-1924 February (Box 198, Folder 2009-2015)
    - W, 1924 February-1935 (Box 199, Folder 2016-2024)
    - X-Z, 1884-1939 (Box 200, Folder 2025-2047)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d., 1887-1893 (Box 201, Folder 2048-2056)
  - Letterbooks
    - 1879-1889 (Box 202, Folder 2057-2060)
    - 1886-1891 (Box 203, Folder 2061-2065)
    - 1889-1895 (Box 204, Folder 2066-2068)
    - 1895-1898 (Box 205, Folder 2069-2071)
    - 1898-1901 (Box 206, Folder 2072-2074)
    - 1913 (Box 207, Folder 2075)
  - Financial papers
    - Account books, 1887-1916 (Box 208, Folder 2076-2077)
    - Bailey Town, undated (Box 209, Folder 2078)
    - Estate, 1874-1899 (Box 210, Folder 2079-2081)
    - Estate, 1886-1918 (Box 211, Folder 2082)
  - Financial circulars
    - A-G, 1896-1926 (Box 212, Folder 2083-2095)
    - H-Q, 1896-1926 (Box 213, Folder 2096-3008)
    - R-Z, 1896-1926 (Box 214, Folder 3009-3019)
  - Writings
    - Books
      - Chapters in the History of Social Legislation in the United States
        - Outlines, correspondence, [ca 1912-1922] (Box 215, Folder 3020)
        - Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 215, Folder 3021)
        - Letters of acknowledgement, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 3022)
        - Drafts for Volume II, undated
          - Chapters 11-13 (Box 215, Folder 3023)
          - Chapters 14-17 (Box 215, Folder 3024)
          - Chapter 19 (Box 215, Folder 3025-3026)
          - Chapter 19 (Box 216, Folder 3027)
          - Chapters 20, 27 (Box 216, Folder 3028)
          - Chapters 28-29 (Box 216, Folder 3029)
          - Chapters 30-31 (Box 216, Folder 3030)
          - Chapters 34-40, misc. (Box 216, Folder 3031)
        - Drafts, notes for Volume II, undated (Box 216, Folder 3032)
        - Drafts, notes for Volume II, undated (Box 217, Folder 3033-3037)
        - Drafts, notes for Volume II, undated (Box 218, Folder 3038-3042)
        - Drafts, notes for Volume II, undated (Box 219, Folder 3043-3044)
        - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 219, Folder 3045)
        - Tables, undated (Box 219, Folder 3046-3049)
          General
          See also: box 313
        - Research material, undated (Box 220, Folder 3050)
        - Henry Farnam
          See: boxes 249-251
        - Looking Backwards
      - Shakespeare's Economics
        - Outlines, notes, [ca l906-1930] (Box 220, Folder 3050)
        - Notes, [ca 1906-1930] (Box 220, Folder 3052)
        - Bibliographical correspondence and notes, [ca 1912-1932] (Box 220, Folder 3053-3054)
        - Correspondence with Yale University Press, 1931 (Box 220, Folder 3055)
        - Correspondence with readers, 1931-1932 (Box 220, Folder 3056)
      - Some Literary Lapses of H.W.F.
      - Tobacco and Economic Efficiency
        See: boxes 283-289
    - Course materials
      - "The Modern Labor Movement", [ca1891-1912]
        - Outlines, bibliographies, exams (Box 221, Folder 3057)
        - Lectures 1-31 (Box 221, Folder 3058-3063)
        - Lectures 32-58 (Box 222, Folder 3064-3068)
        - Notes (Box 222, Folder 3069-3070)
      - "Pauperism and Crime", [ca1897-1907]
        - Outlines, bibliographies, exams (Box 223, Folder 3071)
        - Lectures 1-28 (Box 223, Folder 3072-3076)
        - Notes (Box 223, Folder 3077)
      - "Public Finance"
        - Outlines, bibliographies, exams (Box 224, Folder 3078)
        - Lectures 1-24 (Box 224, Folder 3079-3083)
        - Lectures 25-55 (Box 225, Folder 3084-3089)
        - Lectures 56-58 (Box 226, Folder 3090)
        - Final lectures (Box 226, Folder 3091)
        - Old lectures (Box 226, Folder 3902-3093)
        - Dictation (Box 226, Folder 3094)
        - Notes (Box 226, Folder 3095-3096)
      - "Social Legislation"
        See: boxes 221-226
      - "Social Politics, 1900-1915
        - Outlines, bibliographies, exams (Box 226, Folder 3097)
        - Lectures 1-33 (Box 227, Folder 3098-3104)
        - Lectures 33-57, misc. (Box 228, Folder 3105-3111)
        - Notes, printed matter, lantern slides (Box 229, Folder 3112)
      - Roosevelt Professorship, University of Berlin, 1912-1915
        - Correspondence, lists, printed matter (Box 229, Folder 3113)
        - Clippings (Box 229, Folder 3113)
        - Outlines, lectures 1-4 (Box 229, Folder 3114)
        - Lectures 5-18, misc. (Box 229, Folder 3115-3117)
      - Miscellaneous course materials, 1881-1903
        - Records of course work, notes, accounts (Box 229, Folder 3118)
        - Banking (Box 230, Folder 3119)
        - Capital (Box 230, Folder 3120)
        - The Clergy and Charity (Box 230, Folder 3120)
        - Political Economy (Box 230, Folder 3121)
        - Taxation and Credit (Box 235, Folder 3122)
    - Articles and speeches
      - 1871-1887 (Box 231, Folder 3123-3129)
      - 1887-1894 (Box 232, Folder 3130-3136)
      - 1895-1902 (Box 233, Folder 3137-3142)
      - 1902-1906 (Box 234, Folder 3143-3149)
      - 1906-1911 (Box 235, Folder 3150-3156)
      - 1911-1917 (Box 236, Folder 3157-3162)
      - 1917-1919 (Box 237, Folder 3163-3168)
      - 1919-1920 (Box 238, Folder 3169-3174)
      - 1920-1923 (Box 239, Folder 3175-3181)
      - 1924-1930 (Box 240, Folder 3182-3188)
      - 1931-1933 (Box 241, Folder 3189-3194)
    - German lecture notes
      - 1875-1876 (Box 241, Folder 3195)
      - 1876-1877 (Box 242, Folder 3196-3200)
      - 1877-1878 (Box 243, Folder 3201-3205)
  - Subject Files
    - Alcohol
      - American Section of the International Committee for the Study of the Liquor Problem, 1913 (Box 244, Folder 3206)
      - Committee of Fifty (Box 244, Folder 3207-3212)
        - General, 1896-1899 (Box 244, Folder 3207-3212)
        - Economic sub-committee, 1893-1899 (Box 244, Folder 3207-3212)
      - Prohibition, 1917-1926 (Box 244, Folder 3213-3214)
      - Prohibition, 1917-1926 (Box 245, Folder 3215-3216)
      - Statistics, 1919-1924 (Box 245, Folder 3217)
    - China, 1924-1925 (Box 245, Folder 3218)
    - Civil Service reform
      - New Haven Civil Service Reform Association, 1881-1901 (Box 245, Folder 3219-3221)
      - Connecticut Civil Service Reform Association, 1901-1933 (Box 246, Folder 3222-3227)
      - Connecticut Civil Service Reform Association, 1901-1933 (Box 247, Folder 3228-3229)
      - National Civil Service Reform League, 1884-1926 (Box 247, Folder 3230-3232)
      - Articles and speeches, 1884-1915 (Box 247, Folder 3233-3234)
      - Articles and speeches, 1916-1926 (Box 248, Folder 3235-3238)
    - Economics, 1894-1921 (Box 248, Folder 3239-3240)
    - Farnam family: biographical essay
      - General, [ca 1841-1930] (Box 249, Folder 3241)
      - Farnam, Henry W., 1842-1893 (Box 249, Folder 3242-3247)
      - Farnam, Henry W., 1882-1893 (Box 250, Folder 3248-3253)
      - Farnam, Henry W., 1882-1893 (Box 251, Folder 3254-3256)
      - Silvercruys, Franz, 1925 (Box 251, Folder 3257)
    - German politics, 1879-1904 (Box 251, Folder 3258-3259)
    - Labor legislation
      - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1905-1929 (Box 252, Folder 3260-3267)
      - National Civic Federation, 1900-1902 (Box 252, Folder 3268)
      - Miscellanea, 1899-1929 (Box 253, Folder 3269-3276)
    - Organizations
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1911 (Box 254, Folder 3277)
      - American Association of University Professors, 1915-1928 (Box 254, Folder 3278)
      - American Committee for China Famine Fund, 1920-1921 (Box 254, Folder 3279)
      - American Committee for Relief in the Near East, 1919-1921 (Box 254, Folder 3280)
      - American Economic Association, 1906-1922 (Box 254, Folder 3281-3285)
      - American Embassy Association, 1909-1912 (Box 254, Folder 3286)
      - American Eugenics Association, 1911-1931 (Box 254, Folder 3287)
      - American Friends Service Committee, 1920 (Box 254, Folder 3288)
      - American League to Limit Armaments, 1915-1922 (Box 254, Folder 3289)
      - American Peace Award, 1925-1929 (Box 254, Folder 3290)
      - American Red Star Animal Relief, undated (Box 255, Folder 3291)
      - American Year Book Corporation, 1910-1925 (Box 255, Folder 3292-3293)
      - Americanization Committee of New Haven, 1919-1923 (Box 255, Folder 3294)
      - Board of Research Associates in American Economic History, 1904-1914 (Box 255, Folder 3295-3299)
      - Board of Research Associates in American Economic History, 1904-1914 (Box 256, Folder 3300-3301)
      - Boardmen Training School Fund, 1884-1893 (Box 256, Folder 3302-3305)
      - Calhoun Colored School
        - General, 1904-1916 (Box 256, Folder 3306)
        - General, 1917-1932 (Box 257, Folder 3307)
        - Checks, 1905-1917 (Box 257, Folder 3308)
      - Carnegie Institute of Washington, D.C., 1909-1917 (Box 257, Folder 3309)
      - Central Committee, Inc., 1923 (Box 257, Folder 3310)
      - Century Club, 1883-1897 (Box 257, Folder 3311)
      - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1916-1919 (Box 257, Folder 3312)
      - Chicago Chamber of Commerce, 1886-1887 (Box 257, Folder 3313)
      - Citizenship Conference, 1923 (Box 257, Folder 3314)
      - Civic Federation of New Haven: Anti-Mosquito Campaign, 1912-1913 (Box 257, Folder 3315)
      - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1915-1917 (Box 257, Folder 3316)
      - Committee of Pro-League Independents of Connecticut, 1920 (Box 257, Folder 3317)
      - Committee on Educational Publicity in the Interests of World Peace, 1923-1928 (Box 258, Folder 3318)
      - Committee on the Ross Case, 1900-1901 (Box 258, Folder 3319)
      - Community Service, Inc., 1919 (Box 258, Folder 3320)
      - Congrès des Habitations à Bon Marché, 1910-1924 (Box 258, Folder 3321)
      - Connecticut Chamber of Commerce, 1920-1928 (Box 258, Folder 3322)
      - Connecticut Civic Association, 1905 (Box 258, Folder 3323)
      - Connecticut Commission of Sculpture, 1890-1910 (Box 258, Folder 3324)
      - Connecticut Federation of Churches, 1922-1924 (Box 258, Folder 3325)
      - Connecticut Industrial Commission, 1911-1912 (Box 258, Folder 3326)
      - Connecticut State Conference of Charities and Correction, 1910-1911 (Box 258, Folder 3327)
      - Connecticut State Council of Defense, 1917-1918 (Box 258, Folder 3328)
      - Consumer's League of Connecticut, 1909, 1921-1924 (Box 258, Folder 3329)
      - District of Columbia Fire Department, 1913-1914 (Box 258, Folder 3330)
      - Dixwell Community House, 1923 (Box 258, Folder 3331)
      - Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1926-1928 (Box 258, Folder 3332)
      - George Junior Republic Association, undated (Box 258, Folder 3333)
      - Hopkins Grammar School, 1860-1932 (Box 258, Folder 3334)
      - Hopkins Grammar School, 1860-1932 (Box 259, Folder 3335-3341)
      - Hopkins Grammar School, 1860-1932 (Box 260, Folder 3342-3344)
      - International associations, 1910-1924 (Box 260, Folder 3345-3351)
      - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, Inc., 1922-1932 (Box 261, Folder 3352)
      - League to Enforce Peace, 1915-1922 (Box 261, Folder 3353-3355)
      - Liberal League, 1923-1924 (Box 261, Folder 3356)
      - Lord's Day Alliance, 1920-1921 (Box 261, Folder 3357)
      - Lowell House Association, 1901-1931 (Box 261, Folder 3358-3360)
      - Lowell House Association, 1901-1931 (Box 262, Folder 3361-3366)
      - Lowell House Association, 1901-1931 (Box 263, Folder 3367)
      - Morning News, 1883-1893 (Box 263, Folder 3368-3373)
      - Morning News, 1884-1890 (Box 264, Folder 3374-3376)
      - National Armenian Relief Committee, 1896 (Box 264, Folder 3377)
      - National Housing Association, 1909-1918 (Box 264, Folder 3378)
      - National Security League, 1915-1918 (Box 264, Folder 3379-3380)
      - National Security League, 1917-1918 (Box 265, Folder 3381)
      - National Society of the Colonial Dames of America, undated (Box 265, Folder 3382)
      - New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 1922 (Box 265, Folder 3383)
      - New Haven Community Chest, 1919-1933 (Box 265, Folder 3384-3389)
      - New Haven County Anti-Tuberculosis Association: Gaylord Farm Sanitation, 1904-1920 (Box 266, Folder 3390)
      - New Haven First Church and Society, 1898, 1925-1927 (Box 266, Folder 3391)
      - New Haven Hospital, 1879-1927 (Box 266, Folder 3392-3397)
      - New Haven Hospital, 1887-1928 (Box 267, Folder 3398-3406)
      - New Haven Mayor's Committee on Recruiting, 1917 (Box 268, Folder 3407)
      - New Haven Public Library, 1906 (Box 268, Folder 3408)
      - New Haven Security League, 1917-1918 (Box 268, Folder 3409)
      - New Haven Symphony, 1897-1898 (Box 268, Folder 3410)
      - New Haven War Bureau, 1912 (Box 268, Folder 3411)
      - Oliver, Thomas, Sir: dinner, 1912 (Box 268, Folder 3412)
      - Organized Charities Association, 1893-1909 (Box 268, Folder 3413)
      - Patriotic Service League, undated (Box 268, Folder 3414)
      - Peabody Musuem, 1917 (Box 268, Folder 3415)
      - Penny Provident Fund, 1869-1890; 1913 (Box 268, Folder 3416)
      - Pilgrim Memorial Fund, 1918-1920 (Box 268, Folder 3417)
      - Rotary Club of New Haven, 1917-1920 (Box 268, Folder 3418-3419)
      - Rotary Club of New Haven, 1920-1925 (Box 269, Folder 3420-3424)
      - Serbian Relief Committee of America, 1915-1916 (Box 269, Folder 3425)
      - Settlement League, 1919-1921 (Box 269, Folder 3426-3427)
        See also: boxes 304-305
      - Stable Money Association, undated (Box 270, Folder 3428)
      - Sulgrave Institute, 1919-1921 (Box 270, Folder 3429)
      - Tyringham Forest Club, 1894-1898 (Box 270, Folder 3430)
      - United States Employment Service, 1919 (Box 270, Folder 3431)
      - Universal Races Congress, 1909-1912 (Box 270, Folder 3432)
      - University Club, 1875-1898; 1913 (Box 270, Folder 3433-3434)
      - Washington First Congregational Society Building Fund, 1926 (Box 270, Folder 3435)
      - Woodrow Wilson Foundation, 1921-1923; 1929 (Box 270, Folder 3436-3437)
      - World Alliance for International Friendship Through the Churches, 1922-1928 (Box 270, Folder 3438)
      - Yale Bicentennial Committee, 1901 (Box 271, Folder 3439-3444)
      - Yale Field Corporation, 1881-1891 (Box 271, Folder 3445)
      - Yale-in-China, 1924-1933 (Box 271, Folder 3446-3447)
      - Yale-in-China, 1924-1933 (Box 272, Folder 3448-3450)
      - Yale Review
        - Early papers, 1846-1851 (Box 272, Folder 3451)
        - General, 1887-1918 (Box 272, Folder 3451-3454)
        - Yale Publishing Company, 1892-1906 (Box 273, Folder 3455-3457)
        - Miscellanea, 1892-1904 (Box 273, Folder 3458-3459)
      - Yale University
        - General, 1845-1923 (Box 273, Folder 3460-3461)
        - Class of 1874, 1876-1904 (Box 273, Folder 3462)
        - Class of 1874, 1909-1912 (Box 274, Folder 3463-3470)
        - Class of 1874, 1913-1923 (Box 275, Folder 3471-3478)
        - Class of 1874, 1924-1933 (Box 276, Folder 3479-3484)
        - Committee on University Lectures, 1909-1914 (Box 276, Folder 3485)
        - Committee on University Lectures, 1909-1914 (Box 277, Folder 3486-3489)
        - Connecticut Hall
          See: box 278, folder 3497-3499
        - Corporation, 1876-1934 (Box 277, Folder 3490)
        - Graduate School, 1880-1917 (Box 277, Folder 3491-3492)
        - Graduate School, 1901-1925 (Box 278, Folder 3493-3494)
        - Sheffield Scientific School, 1891-1914 (Box 278, Folder 3495-3496)
        - South Middle College Restoration Committee, 1899-1906 (Box 278, Folder 3497-3499)
        - South Middle College Restoration Committee, 1903-1914 (Box 279, Folder 3500-3506)
        - Student Prizes, 1882-1922 (Box 279, Folder 3507)
        - Sumner, William Graham: Memorial, 1910 (Box 279, Folder 3507)
        - University Library Committee, 1913-1916 (Box 279, Folder 3508)
      - Young Republican Club of New Haven, 1880; 1884 (Box 279, Folder 3509)
    - Photographs
      - Albums: Germany, France, and Denmark, undated (Box 280, Folder 3510-3512)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 281, Folder 3513)
    - Poems: by Henry W. Farnam and others, 1910-1931 (Box 281, Folder 3514)
    - Poor relief
      - New Haven: Town Committee on Workhouse and Poor Relief, 1886-1889 (Box 281, Folder 3515-3518)
      - Connecticut towns, 1887 (Box 282, Folder 3519)
      - United States and Europe, 1887-1888 (Box 282, Folder 3520)
    - Population, 1896-1897 (Box 282, Folder 3521)
    - Tacitus, undated (Box 282, Folder 3522-3523)
    - Tenement houses, 1903-1920 (Box 282, Folder 3524-3525)
    - Tobacco
      - Committee to Study the Tobacco Problem, 1913-1931 (Box 283, Folder 3526-3532)
      - Committee to Study the Tobacco Problem, 1927 (Box 284, Folder 3533)
      - Economic Sub-Committee, 1919-1929 (Box 284, Folder 3534-3539)
      - Economic Sub-Committee, 1919-1929 (Box 285, Folder 3540-3546)
      - Economic Sub-Committee, 1919-1929 (Box 286, Folder 3547-3553)
      - Economic Sub-Committee, 1919-1929 (Box 287, Folder 3554-3560)
      - Economic Sub-Committee, 1919-1929 (Box 288, Folder 3561-3566)
      - Writings and miscellanea, 1913-1929 (Box 289, Folder 3567-3572)
    - Miscellanea, undated
      - Notes (Box 290, Folder 3573-3578)
      - Notes (Box 291, Folder 3579-3584)
      - Notes (Box 292, Folder 3585-3587)
      - Index to clippings files (Box 293, Folder 3585-3587)
      - Index to clippings files (Box 294, Folder 3585-3587)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Civil Service, 1916-1924 (Box 295, Folder 3588)
    - Community Labor Board, 1918-1919 (Box 295, Folder 3589)
    - Entertainment, 1887-1894 (Box 295, Folder 3590-3591)
    - Entertainment, 1894-1905 (Box 296, Folder 3592-3594)
    - Entertainment, 1904-1912 (Box 297, Folder 3595-3597)
    - Entertainment, 1912-1921 (Box 298, Folder 3598-3600)
    - Entertainment, 1921-1926 (Box 299, Folder 3601-3602)